<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Defs>

	<ConceptDef ParentName="NotedOpportunisticBase">
		<defName>AC_SleeveGrowing</defName>
		<label>Growing Sleeves</label>
		<helpText>SLEEVE INCUBATORS can be used to create new sleeves from scratch. It requires NEUTROAMINE as fuel.
		\n\nTo start growing a new sleeve select the sleeve incubator and click CREATE SLEEVE. This will open the sleeve designer. Here you can customize the new sleeve to your liking, choose its race (supports HAR 2.0) and choose its level of QUALITY and BEAUTY. When you are happy with the design, click ACCEPT to start growing the pawn.\n\nBEAUTY defines how beautiful the new sleeve will be. This will add the appropriate trait to the new sleeve. NORMAL will not add beauty trait.
		\n\nQUALITY will influence how long the sleeve takes to grow and apply a hediff that effects how effective the new sleeve is. NORMAL will not add a hediff.
		\n\nNew sleeves are basically brain dead and wont be able to care for themselves. Its recommended to have a SLEEVE CASKET ready to store them until you install a stack.</helpText>
	</ConceptDef>

	<ConceptDef ParentName="NotedOpportunisticBase">
		<defName>AC_UsingSleeveCaskets</defName>
		<label>Sleeve Caskets</label>
		<helpText>SLEEVE CASKETS are Ultratech med beds that induces the sleeve in a cryogenic sleep. This means their needs will not decay and you can take your time installing IMPLANTS and STACKS into new empty sleeves.</helpText>
	</ConceptDef>

	<ConceptDef ParentName="NotedOpportunisticBase">
		<defName>AC_UsingBrainTemplates</defName>
		<label>Brain Templates</label>
		<helpText>BRAIN TEMPLATES are new items you can insert into SLEEVE CASKETS to modify sleeves grown inside with special values, giving them HEDIFFS that make the new sleeve more useful for certain tasks.
		\n\nTo inset a brain template, select the wanted SLEEVE INCUBATOR and click on INSERT BRAIN TEMPLATE. Now you can select what kind of template you want (It will only show templates available to you!). One of your colonists will automatically insert the template for you now.
		\n\nYou can remove a template from a sleeve incubator by selecting it and saying REMOVE TEMPLATE NAME.</helpText>
	</ConceptDef>

	<ConceptDef ParentName="NotedOpportunisticBase">
		<defName>AC_EmptyStacks</defName>
		<label>Cortical Stacks</label>
		<helpText>CORTICAL STACKS are a new IMPLANT you can install in any pawn via SURGERY. They store the pawns consciousness and prevent them from dying if their body is destroyed.
		\n\nIn game terms this means: When a empty stack is installed, it saves the pawns data on it. This includes, but is not limited to: name, age, traits (not all, some are excluded!), skills, relationships, bonds, and much more! Including ROYALTY DLC information.
		\nIt also supports multiple popular mods by default.
		\n\nWhen a pawn with a stack dies, you can EXTRACT the stack from the corpse via either the new EXTRACT STACK ORDER or simply right clicking a pawn with a colonist selected. Similarly to how stripping clothes work.
		\n\nCORTICAL STACKS can't be crafted. You will have to find or "acquire" them from pawns.
		\n\nCORTICAL STACKS can be DUPLICATED. This makes an exact copy of the pawn on STACK ONE to a new empty stack, STACK TWO. Be careful, not everyone likes being cloned. To DUPLICATE a stack, select a colonist and click on the stack you want to duplicate. This requires a pawn with at least an INTELLECTUAL skill of 10. Be aware, this can fail and destroy the stack!</helpText>
	</ConceptDef>

	<ConceptDef ParentName="NotedOpportunisticBase">
		<defName>AC_FilledStacks</defName>
		<label>Filled Stacks</label>
		<helpText>FILLED CORTICAL STACKS are stacks with a pawns consciousness stored on them.
		\n\nAs long as the stack with a pawn stored on it exists, the pawn on it is considerd alive by the game. You can IMPLANT filled stacks into a new body (or sleeve if you want) via SURGERY. This can be ANYONE, even a PRISONER! Due to game limitations, you cant select which stack you want to install, so its recommended you FORBID all filled stacks you have BUT the one you want to install.
		\n\nFILLED CORTICAL STACKS can also be WIPED and turned into EMPTY CORTICAL STACKS. This progress kills the pawn stored on it. To WIPE a stack, select a colonist and then click on the stack you want to wipe. This requires a pawn with at least an INTELLECTUAL skill of 10. Be aware, this can fail and destroy the stack!
		\n\nCORTICAL STACKS can't be crafted. You will have to find or "acquire" them from other pawns.</helpText>
	</ConceptDef>

	<ConceptDef ParentName="NotedOpportunisticBase">
		<defName>AC_DeadPawnWithStack</defName>
		<label>Extract Stacks</label>
		<helpText>It seems you have corpses with CORTICAL STACKS on your map!
		\n\nYou can EXTRACT the stack from the corpse via either the new EXTRACT STACK ORDER or simply right clicking a pawn with a colonist selected. Similarly to how stripping clothes work.
		\n\nStacks are rare and powerful, so make sure to harvest them!</helpText>
	</ConceptDef>

</Defs>
